>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好，我们来谈谈这个模块的练习，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right,
let's talk about this module's exercise,
我们会通过一个解决方案
we'll walk through a solution to it.
当自述文件显示时，您希望执行以下功能 :
As the ReadMe lays out, you want to take
these functions, the ones that are at
底部，并基本将它们包裹在一个称为 " 定义研讨会" 的大型函数中。
the bottom, and essentially wrap them in
one big function called define workshop.
这将是我们的模块工厂功能。
That'll be our module factory function.
所以我开始做这个，我要说 defineWorkshop。
So I'll start by doing that,
I'll say defineWorkshop.
这一巨大的功能将包括其中的所有内容。
And this one big function is going to
include all of these inside of it.
就像其他的一样
And so just like with the other ones,
我会在这个范围的底部保留这些功能。
I'll keep those functions at
the bottom of that scope.
我要做一个公共 API
I'm gonna make and return a public API.
>> Kyle Simpson: 然后，我还需要此模块的一些数据以关闭使用。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then I also need some
data for this module to close over to use.
我要结束的数据就是 currentEnrollment 和
And the data that I'm gonna be
closing over is currentEnrollment and
studentRecords，我需要这里的两个阵列。
studentRecords, I need those
two arrays Inside of here.
所以我会安排和安排 currentEnrollment ，
So I will make and
arrange called currentEnrollment,
>> Kyle Simpson: 另一个已调用
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Another one called
studentRecords， >> Kyle Simpson: 在我的公用 API上，
studentRecords,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: On my public API,
我需要根据自述文件的要求
I need to have according to the ReadMe,
这五个功能， addStudent 和 enrollStudents。
these five functions,
addStudent and enrollStudents.
所以，让我们先做这些，然后定义这些。
So, let's do those first and define those.
>> Kyle Simpson: 如何工作?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: How do those work?
首先我们有 addStudent
Well, first, we have addStudent.
它会把 ID和名字以及他们的报酬
It's gonna take the ID, the name and
whether they're paid and
创造出一个记录和其他的东西
create a record and stuff that in.
所以我们要把 id和名字
So, we're gonna take id, name,
并作为输入支付。
and paid as the input.
我们要把它推到树桩上
And we're going to push
into the studentRecords
数组， >> Kyle Simpson: 一个对象
array,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: An object that
包括 id， name和付费。
includes id, name, and paid.
>> Kyle Simpson: EnrollStudent 相似，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: EnrollStudent is similar,
学生， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
enrollStudent,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Takes a student id,
并将其推送到 currentEnrollment 数组中。
and it pushes that into
the currentEnrollment array.
我要做一次额外的检查因为这是 API 而不是被设置
I'm gonna do one extra check since this
is an API now rather than being set up,
我要做个额外的检查确保我不会想
it's I'm gonna do an extra check that
makes sure that I'm not try to add
阵列中存在重复的标识。
duplicate IDs into the array.
那我就去吧
So I will do if
(!currentEnrollment.包含(id)，和
(!currentEnrollment.includes(id), and
currentEnrollment.push (id)。
currentEnrollment.push(id).
自述文件随后表示，我们需要一个 printCurrentEnrollment 。
ReadMe then says we need
a printCurrentEnrollment.
那么，打印货币的内容是什么 ?
So what would printCurrenEenrollment do?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 它没有任何投入，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It
doesn't take any inputs,
它基本上占据了这个电话的位置
it essentially takes
the place of this call.
这个是打印 currentEnrollment ，所以
This one is printing
the currentEnrollment, so
让我们把它复制到我们的 printCurrentEnrollment 中
let's literally just copy that
into our printCurrentEnrollment.
我们不希望他们提供他们自己的身份证清单
We don't want them to provide
their own list of IDs,
因为这个模块的目的就是把细节和细节
because that's the whole purpose of
the module is to abstract that detail and
把它作为一个隐藏的实施，好吗 ?
keep it as a hidden implementation, okay?
接下来，自述文件中说我们需要一个注册学生。
Next the readme says we
need an enrollPaidStudents.
一模一样的学生都和这件事一样
Exactly the same, enrollPaidStudents
is doing the same thing as this,
就是叫有酬学生报名，
which is to call paid students to enroll,
and
然后用它更新当前的注册队列。
then update the current
enrollment array with it.
那么，让我们做， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
So, let's do,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What's
它再次调用了注册学生
it called again, enrollPaidStudent.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 最后，我们需要一个学生。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then finally,
we need a remindUnpaidStudents.
同样地，这基本上是取代了这个地方，
Again, that is basically taking the place,
使用我们的 currentEnrollment 调用reminidUn薪。
of calling remindUnpaid
with our currentEnrollment.
所以我们需要这个， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 还有一个功能。
So we need that,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And a function.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，我们现在已在模块内部隐藏这些实施详细信息
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So we've now hidden those
implementation details inside of a module
定义。
definition.
我们有， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
We have,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So,
我们公开了五种公共空气污染指数
we expose five public API methods and
we keep everything else private.
我们保留数据隐私，关闭状态是我们在一段时间内保持该状态的方式。
We keep the data private, and closure is
how we maintain that state over time.
最后一步，然后是 >> Kyle Simpson: Setting
Last step, then, is instead of,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Setting
这些阵列我们需要进行实际的制作和实例化
up these arrays we need to actually
make and instantiate, I guess is not
最后一个步骤，但是下一步，我们是否需要实例化我们的研讨会。
the last step but the next step,
is we need to instantiate our workshop.
所以我们要叫 defineWorkshop ，我们要开始使用它。
So we're gonna call defineWorkshop,
and we're gonna start using it.
我们先给学生记录
We'll first set up the student records,
所以我要去因为我超级懒惰
so I'm going to, because I'm super lazy,
请使用一些正则表达式替换来定义这些表达式。
use some regular expression
replacing to define those.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我已经为自己写了一个
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I have one
already written for myself so
我不需要重写它
I don't have to rewrite it.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我需要开启正则表达式方式。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I need to turn
on regular expression mode.
好了现在这些都是我的功能了
All right, so
now those are all my function calls.
>> Kyle Simpson: 然后在此，我们将调用 deepJS.enrollStudent 。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then similarly here
we're gonna call deepJS.enrollStudent.
这就是我所谓的学生吗
That's what I called it,
right, enrollStudent?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right,
我就把这些都输入出去
I'll just type these out.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在事情已经结束了，剩下的就是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now that stuff's done,
and then all that's left is for
我们要更新这些电话
us to update these calls to print,
>> Kyle Simpson: PrintCurrentEnrollment 。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: PrintCurrentEnrollment.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我想我错过了一个细节。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think
I missed a detail there.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不仅要更新它，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I not only
need to update it, but
我们要打印记录，所以我错过了这个 [ INAUDIBLE]。
we need to print the records,
so I missed that [INAUDIBLE].
我们的注册学生需要更新注册并打印这些记录。
Our enroll paid students needs to update
the enrollment and print those records.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我们调用 deepJS.enrollPaidStudents。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We call
deepJS.enrollPaidStudents.
然后是最后一个但不重要的是 ddeepJS。RemindUnpaidSod学生们。
And then last but not least,
ddeepJS.RemindUnpaidSstudents.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们完成了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And we're done.
我一开始就说模块真的是最重要的代码之一
As I said at the outset, modules really
is one of the most important code
所有 JavaScript中的组织模式，可能在所有软件中，
organization patterns in all of
JavaScript, maybe in all of software,
但在所有 JavaScript中都是这样
but certainly in all of JavaScript.
这样你就会得到很多关于这个模式的想法
So you're gonna get a lot of mileage
out of thinking about this pattern,
正在练习，尝试更有效的实施。
practicing it,
trying to implement it more.
所以我强烈建议在这个过程中确定一切
So I would strongly recommend
everything in this course for sure but
尤其是这个
especially this.
如果你愿意回去做些作业
Try to go back and
do some homework, if you will.
你试着回去找
Try to go back and look for
在您的代码中有一些地方可以使用更完善的组织和
some place in your code where that
could use some better organization and
看看是否有办法为一个模块提取一个简单的定义。
see if there's a way to extract out
a simple definition for a module.